{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Gravel Paving \u0026 Installation Services","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/40126/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40126,"taskName":"Gravel or Loose Fill Paving - Install, Spread or Scrape","taskDescription":"Install, Spread or Scrape Gravel or Loose Fill Paving","xmTaskDescriptor":"Gravel Paving \u0026 Installation Services","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":61,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Gravel Paving Fill Loose Spread","textMessagingName":"Install Loose Fill","rolloverLongDesc":"Gravel is brought in by truck \u0026 spread with a backhoe, grader or bulldozer. Includes adding gravel \u0026/or re-smoothing the surface later on. May include installation of culverts.","rolloverShortDesc":"For roads, driveways paths \u0026 parking.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Install, Spread or Scrape Gravel or Loose Fill Paving.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Gravel Paving Installation \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Spread or Scrape Gravel","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":56,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":5,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Gravel or Loose Fill Paving Install","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Gravel or Loose Fill Paving - Install, Spread or Scrape","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Gravel Paving Project","urlName":"Gravel-Installation-Spread-or-Scrape","taskConsiderationId":2,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Gravel Pavers - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor Gravel Spreading, Scraping \u0026 Installation","searchKeywords":"Gravel, Paving, patio, driveway, pave, mason, paver","emcCategoryOid":-12055,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":437,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40126/":{"taskOID":40126,"originalTaskOID":40126,"setID":437,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":5727,"questionDisplayText":"Nature of Project","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the nature of this project? (Select all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3266,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Install new loose fill","answerDisplayText":"Install new loose fill","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5166,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Remove loose fill","answerDisplayText":"Remove loose fill","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5219,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Repair existing loose fill","answerDisplayText":"Repair or maintain existing loose fill area","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1292,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Loose Fill","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of loose fill do you want?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":1466,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Cobblestone","answerDisplayText":"Cobblestone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1727,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Crushed rock","answerDisplayText":"Crushed rock","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2846,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Gravel","answerDisplayText":"Gravel","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4626,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Pebbles","answerDisplayText":"Pebbles","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5365,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Road base","answerDisplayText":"Road base","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5366,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Rock","answerDisplayText":"Rock","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5466,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Sand","answerDisplayText":"Sand","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7064,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Wood chips","answerDisplayText":"Wood chips","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10617,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Want Recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Want Recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1291,"questionDisplayText":"Description of Area","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Select the best description of the area you need covered.","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2086,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Driveway","answerDisplayText":"Driveway","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6733,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Walkway or sidewalk","answerDisplayText":"Walkway or sidewalk","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4604,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Patio","answerDisplayText":"Patio","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4729,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Playground","answerDisplayText":"Playground","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6142,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Stream bed","answerDisplayText":"Stream bed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4774,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Pond","answerDisplayText":"Pond","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4578,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Parking lot","answerDisplayText":"Parking lot","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":5727,"questionDisplayText":"Nature of Project","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the nature of this project? (Select all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3266,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Install new loose fill","answerDisplayText":"Install new loose fill","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5166,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Remove loose fill","answerDisplayText":"Remove loose fill","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5219,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Repair existing loose fill","answerDisplayText":"Repair or maintain existing loose fill area","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":3266,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Install new loose fill","answerDisplayText":"Install new loose fill","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5166,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Remove loose fill","answerDisplayText":"Remove loose fill","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5219,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Repair existing loose fill","answerDisplayText":"Repair or maintain existing loose fill area","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1292,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Loose Fill","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of loose fill do you want?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":1466,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Cobblestone","answerDisplayText":"Cobblestone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1727,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Crushed rock","answerDisplayText":"Crushed rock","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2846,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Gravel","answerDisplayText":"Gravel","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4626,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Pebbles","answerDisplayText":"Pebbles","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5365,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Road base","answerDisplayText":"Road base","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5366,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Rock","answerDisplayText":"Rock","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5466,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Sand","answerDisplayText":"Sand","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7064,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Wood chips","answerDisplayText":"Wood chips","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10617,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Want Recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Want Recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":1466,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Cobblestone","answerDisplayText":"Cobblestone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1727,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Crushed rock","answerDisplayText":"Crushed rock","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2846,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Gravel","answerDisplayText":"Gravel","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4626,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Pebbles","answerDisplayText":"Pebbles","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5365,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Road base","answerDisplayText":"Road base","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5366,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Rock","answerDisplayText":"Rock","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5466,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Sand","answerDisplayText":"Sand","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7064,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Wood chips","answerDisplayText":"Wood chips","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10617,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Want Recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Want Recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1291,"questionDisplayText":"Description of Area","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Select the best description of the area you need covered.","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2086,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Driveway","answerDisplayText":"Driveway","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6733,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Walkway or sidewalk","answerDisplayText":"Walkway or sidewalk","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4604,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Patio","answerDisplayText":"Patio","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4729,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Playground","answerDisplayText":"Playground","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6142,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Stream bed","answerDisplayText":"Stream bed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4774,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Pond","answerDisplayText":"Pond","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4578,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Parking lot","answerDisplayText":"Parking lot","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":2086,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Driveway","answerDisplayText":"Driveway","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6733,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Walkway or sidewalk","answerDisplayText":"Walkway or sidewalk","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4604,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Patio","answerDisplayText":"Patio","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4729,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Playground","answerDisplayText":"Playground","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6142,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Stream bed","answerDisplayText":"Stream bed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4774,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Pond","answerDisplayText":"Pond","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4578,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Parking lot","answerDisplayText":"Parking lot","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"isCookielessUser":true}